today we're gonna be giving away 50 000
cookies at one of our food drives
let me explain we're gonna drive out to
a small county where 35
of the people live below the poverty
line and we're literally gonna give out
food to
any family that needs it normally in a
food drive like this we would pack a
thousand boxes of food and give them
away but this food drives a little
different because this tick tocker right
here molad for whatever reason felt
compelled to bake
50 000 cookies and donated to peace
philanthropy which is why in this food
drive they're also going to get 15 to 20
cookies
i just want to show you guys real quick
how much food every single person is
getting they're literally getting milk
apples meat yogurt bunch of vegetables a
ton of pantry stuff
every single car you see here is getting
three boxes of food
pack of cookies as many yams as they can
carry
[Music]
truck gets seven here you go mr macho
man over there
uh-huh you want another one i think i
can still stand
right there you go darren look at me i
carried a bunch of boxes good effort
i thought of it heaven what did the one
say to that i don't know but it better
be funny how you been
really touched by how many lives we're
changing here today i thought it would
maybe be 50 cars i don't see the end of
the line of cars yet so it is really a
huge impact
i got another one what did the beans say
to the sand dunes another big
what are you being doing the same joke
for the rest of the video darren's
banned from making jokes
on a scale from one to ten i think this
food drive is a ten i think it's helping
a lot of people in the community that
are in need and especially in the
pandemic i have never seen 50 000
cookies
you understand we have to get rid of 50
000 cookies we got chocolate chips
oatmeal raisins raspberry cheesecake and
that's it because you know nut allergies
exist
carrying all these cookies can i give
these to you thank you
how many chocolate chips do you think
they just got
enjoyed the cookies okay i don't know
what you're gonna do with all those
cookies all at once but there you go
here can i just hand it to these guys
i hope you guys have a good
to your main day oh i appreciate it if
you turn around you'll see a blue van
the little kid in the back is super cool
i want you to give them as many cookies
as you can you gotta give them a lot of
cookies
i got this whole box of cookies just for
you these are all cookies
this is sheila she helped us organize
his food drive location and is in
general a huge support to this community
and we wanted to surprise her with
something she could give back to the
community if you could just stand right
here
just face that direction give us one
second faster driver turn around
we brought 25 laptops for you to uh give
way to people in the community oh my god
thank you these laptops are going to
help so many people and i'm so excited
25 years
aaron was telling me how we saw a lot of
comments on the last video like why did
this person with a nice car need food or
why did this person get so many boxes
i know it's been eating at him so darren
explain you never know what the
circumstances in a person's life it's a
lot of people picking up food for other
people that don't have
cars that can't get here they're taking
it back to their communities and sharing
it there
things are winding down and we still
have some boxes left we would rather
bring too much food than too little
imagine if cars pulled up and we're like
oh we're out of food we feel terrible so
we always try to bring extra food that
way we can feed everyone that comes guys
look who i'm giving you a free cookie
too do you want a free cookie thank you
so much
i appreciate it man and not only did he
give me a free cookie he gave me 50
000 cookies if you want to make a tick
tock with me just donate 50 000 cookies
to be philanthropy even though we gave
away tens of thousands of cookies in
this food drive we still had some left
over at the end so he decided to hit up
a couple of other local communities and
give them the rest of the cookies we
visited the boys and girls club from
the last video a church a local soup
kitchen and they seem very happy to
receive thousands of cookies
if you enjoyed what you saw today and
you and you want to support our food
pantry in the future click the link in
description and buy the brand new beast
philanthropy merch 100 of my revenue
from the beast philanthropy merch the
beast philanthropy channel and the brand
deals on this channel go straight into
this charity buy our awesome merch or
i'm gonna be really sad